<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<gallery>
	<item>
		<title>BRYAN ADAMS</title>
		<description><![CDATA[WONDERWALL. David Ryan Adams (born November 5, 1974) is an American alt-country/rock singer-songwriter from Jacksonville, North Carolina. Initially part of the group Whiskeytown, Ryan Adams left the band to pursue a solo career, releasing Heartbreaker in 2000. A longtime resident of New York City, Adams is probably best known for his song "New York, New York" off his critically acclaimed second album, Gold. He has since released five more solo albums and five albums with backing band The Cardinals. <a href='http://www.ryan-adams.com/' target='_blank' ><font color='#FF0025'> RYAN ADAMS OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_1.jpg</image>
		<video></video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>TOM PETTY</title>
		<description><![CDATA[AMERICAN GIRL. Thomas Earl "Tom" Petty (born October 20, 1950) is an American singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He is the frontman of Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers and was a founding member of the late 1980s supergroup Traveling Wilburys and Mudcrutch. He has also performed under the pseudonyms of Charlie T. Wilbury, Jr. and Muddy Wilbury. <a href='http://tompetty.com/' target='_blank' ><font color='#FF0025'> TOM PETTY OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_2.jpg</image>
		<video>/data/videos/video_2.flv</video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>RAZORLIGHT</title>
		<description><![CDATA[WHO NEEDS LOVE. Razorlight are an English indie rock band formed in 2002. They are primarily known in the UK, having topped the charts with the 2006 single "America" and its parent self-titled album, their second. The band consists of lead singer and rhythm guitarist Johnny Borrell, drummer David 'Skully' Sullivan Kaplan, bass player Freddie Stitz and lead guitarist Gus Robertson.  <a href='http://razorlight.co.uk/' target='_blank' ><font color='#FF0025'> RAZORLIGHT OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_3.jpg</image>
		<video></video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>THE WATERBOYS</title>
		<description><![CDATA[THE WHOLE OF THE MOON. The Waterboys are a Scottish band formed in 1983 by Mike Scott. The band's membership, past and present, has been composed mainly of musicians from Scotland, Ireland and England. Edinburgh, London, Dublin, Spiddal, New York, and Findhorn have all served as homes for the group. The band has played in a number of different styles, but their music is a mix of Celtic folk music with rock and roll. After ten years of recording and touring, they dissolved in 1993 and Scott pursued a solo career. They reformed in 2000, and continue to release albums and tour worldwide. <a href="http://www.mikescottwaterboys.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> THE WATERBOYS OFFICIAL SITE</font></a> ]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_4.jpg</image>
		<video></video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>ARCADE FIRE</title>
		<description><![CDATA[SPRAWL II. Arcade Fire is an indie rock band based in Montreal, Quebec, Canada. It consists of the husband and wife duo of Win Butler and Régine Chassagne, along with Will Butler, Richard Reed Parry, Tim Kingsbury, Jeremy Gara, and Sarah Neufeld. Arcade Fire came to prominence when they released their debut album Funeral in 2004 to critical acclaim. The band plays guitar, drums, bass guitar, piano, violin, viola, cello, double bass, xylophone, glockenspiel, keyboard, French horn, accordion, harp, mandolin, and hurdy-gurdy. Most of their instruments are taken on tour, and the multi-instrumentalist band members switch duties throughout shows. <a href="http://arcadefire.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> ARCADE FIRE OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_5.jpg</image>
		<video></video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>LOQUILLO Y LOS INTOCABLES</title>
		<description><![CDATA[ROCK AND ROLL STAR. José María Sanz Beltrán, Loquillo or Loco (born 21 December 1960) is a Spanish rock singer. He was born in Barcelona. <a href="http://www.loquillo.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> LOQUILLO OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_6.jpg</image>
		<video>/data/videos/video_6.flv</video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>HAPPY MONDAYS</title>
		<description>
      <![CDATA[24 HOUR PARTY PEOPLE. Happy Mondays are an English alternative rock band from Salford, Greater Manchester. Formed in 1980, the band's original line-up was Shaun Ryder on lead vocals, his brother Paul Ryder on bass, lead guitarist Mark Day, keyboardist Paul Davis, and drummer Gary Whelan. Mark "Bez" Berry would later join the band onstage during a live performance after befriending Shaun Ryder and served as a dealer. Rowetta Satchell joined the band to provide backing vocals in the early 1990s. <a href="http://www.happymondaysonline.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> HAPPY MONDAYS OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_7.jpg</image>
		<video></video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>MAKE THE GIRL DANCE</title>
		<description><![CDATA[KILL ME. <a href="http://www.happymondaysonline.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> MAKE THE GIRL DANCE OFFICIAL MYSPACE</font></a]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_8.jpg</image>
		<video>/data/videos/video_8.flv</video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>THE KNIFE</title>
		<description><![CDATA[PASS THIS ON. The Knife are an electronic music duo from Sweden, formed in 1999.[2] The group consist of siblings Karin Dreijer Andersson and Olof Dreijer, who together also run their own record company, Rabid Records. They first received international attention after their song "Heartbeats", covered by José González, appeared in a commercial by Sony. Subsequent songs have appeared on a number of television shows. Their first tour took place in 2006, as well as the release of their critically acclaimed album Silent Shout. They have won a number of Swedish Grammis, but refuse to attend awards ceremonies. They have appeared in public wearing Venetian masks. <a href="http://www.theknife.net/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> THE KNIFE OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_9.jpg</image>
		<video>/data/videos/video_9.flv</video>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>EDITORS</title>
		<description><![CDATA[PAPILLON. Editors are a British indie rock band based in Birmingham, who formed in 2002. Previously known as Pilot, The Pride and Snowfield, the band consists of Tom Smith (lead vocals, rhythm guitar, piano), Chris Urbanowicz (lead guitar, synthesizer), Russell Leetch (bass guitar, backing vocals) and Ed Lay (drums, percussion). <a href="http://www.editorsofficial.com/" target="_blank"><font color="#FF0025"> EDITORS OFFICIAL SITE</font></a>]]></description>
		<image>/data/images/topten/pic_10.jpg</image>
		<video>/data/videos/video_9.flv</video>
	</item>
</gallery>
</root>
